Seino, Galgal Channel GOGO!
Today's project will be Marumaru Sensei Part 1!
Part 1!
Let's do a new project!
I'll be the teacher today!
I'm going to teach in Amikomi.
I'm going to be a teacher and teach at Amikomi.
Basically, when we do release events, we do our own hair.
I used to be in the Drummer Warrior series.
When I was in the Drummer Warrior series, I played the role of an amikomi.
When I really wanted to do it myself, I worked hard and became able to do it.
I worked hard and became able to do it.
I think there are a lot of kids who can do it.
I'd like to teach you how to do it my way, too.
I'd like to teach you how to do it.
By the way, how many of you can do amikomi at this point?
I don't know.
I can't.
If it's other people's...
That's how I'd like to do it.
Today, this person...
What's his name?
Mr. Brubé.
His face is really red.
My face is pretty red.
If you're red, you're not a Bourbe.
I'd say she's more Yves.
You're Yaybe? That's...
Blush? Let's go with red.
Blush.
Sekabe-san.
Sekabe yosami.
Who?
I didn't say.
Then we'll hire this Yoshi Akabe.
Yes, sir.
Well, when I do that, I usually split it down the middle.
First, split it in two.
Akabe-san's hair tends to get tangled in the bottom part.
When I braid it, I usually take the top part like this.
And then, like this, I...
I divide it into three parts.
Okay, okay.
And then...
Yes, yes.
Depending on whether you want it bumpy or not, there's back knitting, front knitting, and so on.
I want to make it bumpy, so I'm going to knit the back.
I'm going to start from the bottom.
The basic method is to bring the outer knit to the center.
Bring the outer one to the center, and then bring the outer one to the center.
Repeat this process.
In the case of a braid, when you put in the braid, you also take the rest of the paper from here.
Put this paper and this end paper together and put them in the middle.
Then, next, on this side, you take the paper from this end and the paper here.
Like this.
Looks hard, doesn't it?
You're saying, "Ouch, ouch, ouch.
I can feel pressure in my neck.
Are you okay?
Hang in there, Mr. Akabe.
It feels like he's being pulled a lot.
But it's so cute.
It's going to look a lot more braided at this point.
One thing to keep in mind when you take them together...
If you take them straight and parallel, you can get a beautiful braided look.
so it will come up nicely.
Also, you can make this amount of braid as much as possible.
It's so cute!
Wow!
Oh, I'm a little off here, but...
Like this.
Oh, it's so beautiful!
Nice. - Nice.
Is the beginning the most important part? In this braid.
It's more important to get the right amount.
And this part right here.
The part you're holding here.
If it gets loose the next time you take it out...
If you take it out next time, it will come out.
Oh, it's loose.
Right, right, right.
And then, at the end, I want you to pull up the rest of this hair
So, at the end, you should pull the rest of the hair up a little bit and then tie it off.
It's harder for the hair to sag here later.
Wow.
So that's about it. Amazing.
It's hard, actually.
It's still hard.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
What did you say? What did you say?
What did you say? Oh, Ty.
It's hard to do. It took me a while to get used to it.
It took me a while to get used to it, and the capacity changes between when I do it and when other people do it.
You do everything? Yes, and I do it myself. It was originally for me, so I started out doing it myself.
Is it that hard for you? I'm a total mess, so even now, I find it easier to work with others.
Yeah, it's cute. If I do it this way, it'll look like this.
I guess that's how I do it.
Do you want to practice? Can you make a fair?
What do you want to do? What do you want to do? Okay, here you go.
Oh, my God! You're a pretty hard-headed teacher! You're a pretty throwaway teacher!
Go ahead! Are you hard on her?
But you have long hair, so I heard it's kind of hard to do.
The make-up artist told me that.
I think your hair might be a little hard to work with.
I can do that.
It's okay if it's thin. Not as thin as possible, but thin to a certain degree.
If you take too much, you won't be able to make steps.
Then you can put this at the end here.
And then I'm going to put it in the middle, in between the two.
I'm afraid, it's something totally different.
Hey.
I was just saying.
Just do it. It's a primer.
This one's right.
Something's missing four stitches.
What? Why?
There aren't four knots.
I made a mistake.
Put them down.
Yes, sir.
Yes, yes.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
And now you can put this between here and here.
How's that?
Take this one and this one.
What's that?
Almost at the bottom.
Oh, yeah.
What is it? I'm starting to rearrange things.
I'm starting to hide my mistakes.
Sir, this way, please.
Here you go.
There you go.
Oh, it's okay.
No, it's fine.
It's fine.
I've already started arranging.
Oh!
A little bit.
Yay.
That's nice.
Cute!
Cute.
You really think so?
I do.
You can't hear me.
And I feel like I don't remember anything.
I had an elastic and I was finished, so I did it.
I think the key is this hair here, a little bit off the braid.
It's very difficult to do, so please try to imitate me.
I finished it.
The point is that it is difficult to arrange because I am also a little late and I don't want to put it out here.
I think you put out too much hair.
The hairs sticking out a little here.
This one is better.
I can't do this.
One hundred and eleven?
Where did you get the eleven hundred?
Oh, 89 out of 10.
Ten out of eighty-nine.
Ah.
It's 100 yen.
Yes.
Here we go.
Ah, this way.
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Stop it!
Please, come in.
Hey, over here.
Here.
It's like no tracing.
How do you do it?
Okay, like this.
Do you need a comb?
I forgot.
Here you go.
Is that a forest? Like a forest. Like a forest.
Yes, thank you.
Is there any part you would like to keep?
Just leave this part.
We can do it until we get in.
Let's do it.
Yes, let's do it.
They're bringing them in at a special price.
I'm scared.
Let him in this far.
Already, Minami, you know, don't you love clunners?
This one's knitted the other way, the way that doesn't make it bumpy.
It fits from the top, too, so...
Sorry, sorry, I heard what you said.
I meant symmetry.
You said my face is scary.
You don't like it.
You don't like it... any more than you did before, when you smiled.
You're not smiling anymore.
You're good.
Yeah.
I'm not kidding.
That's great.
That's why it's so cool.
I've never done this before. Wow! It's my first time! Wow!
What about you, Mi-yi? As expected of you, Kiyo. You're like an open weave.
It's so beautiful, I can feel it.
Isn't it nice? It's good.
It's done!
Yay, it's done!
I'm not sure if this is the body of the chart, but I took it seriously at first.
But this first part is the hardest part.
It's so thin... just the top.
But it's really good!
I'm so good at it!
Amazing!
Minami, you did this side from the top to the back.
She was able to pull it off, but the way she did it, she did it so beautifully.
I made a mistake with my hand.
You're right.
I'm going to practice a little more.
Wow!
That was easy.
You're right, the youngest is better.
That's when he started yelling.
I don't know what to do... this is not good!
I'm glad we had such a good time teaching.
I'm glad I was able to have fun teaching you this way.
Please give it a try and I'll do my best!
Thank you very much for watching.
If you like my braiding skills, please leave a comment and give me a good comment!
This time, I'm wearing Bigo's outfit!